I is in here the top stories for the
나는 여기에있는 최고의 이야기이다.
week of November 7 2016 three years
2016 년 11 월 7 일 3 주
Twitter announced Thursday that it's
트위터는 목요일에
killing off the vine short video
덩굴 짧은 비디오를 죽이는
platform in the coming months when
플랫폼을 다음 달에
Twitter launched the micro video feature
트위터는 마이크로 비디오 기능을 시작했다.
back in 2013 it quickly became a viral
2013 년에 다시 바이러스 성이되었습니다.
enigma challenging users to cram as much
사용자가 많은 것을 벼락치기에 도전하는 수수께끼
comedy or culture into each 480 x 480
코미디 또는 문화를 각 480 x 480
pixel frame users will still be able to
픽셀 프레임 사용자 는 여전히
keep and view their vines in the
유지하고 자신의 포도 나무를 볼 수
announcement fine says to all the
고사는 모든 사람들에게 말한다.
creators out there thank you for taking
거기 제작자 주셔서 감사합니다
a chance on this app back in the day
이 앱에 대한 기회가 다시 생겼다.
back in the day being three years ago
3 년 전의 일
long time ago the surface enjoyed 200
오래 전에 표면이 200을 즐겼다.
million users in 2015 some of its
2015 년에 백만 명의 사용자가
biggest superstars include Canadian
가장 큰 슈퍼 스타는 캐나다
board Andrew kingbach bachelor with more
Andrew kingbach 총각 학사
than 16 million followers and
1600 만명의 추종자와
toronto-based singer-songwriter shawn
토론토에 기반을 둔 싱어 송 라이터 숀
mendes vine videos arguably created its
논쟁의 여지가없이 포도 나무 비디오를 만들었습니다.
own genre of meme thanks to the hypnotic
최면에 대한 감사 덕분에 자신의 장르
nature of its six-second clips that loop
반복하는 6 초 클립의 특성
by default vine co-founder russ Yusupov
기본적으로 포도 나무 공동 창업자 인 russ Yusupov
has little positive to say about the
에 대해 말할 수있는
shutdown tweeting don't sell your
shutdown tweeting은 판매하지 않습니다.
company shortly after the announcement
발표 직후 회사
Yusupov along with co-founders Don
공동 설립자 Don과 함께 Yusupov
Hoffman and Colin Kroll sold vine to
호프만 (Hoffman)과 콜린 크롤 (Colin Kroll)은 포도 나무를
Twitter in 2012 before it's wide release
폭 넓은 출시 전 2012 년 Twitter
I love the little vine loops so I'm I am
나는 작은 포도 나무 루프를 좋아해 그래서 나는
sad I will watch them always as long as
슬픈 나는만큼 항상 그들을 볼 것이다
I can so hopefully somebody else picks
다른 사람들이 고를 수 있기를 바랍니다.
up the company i don't know what i don't
나는 내가 모르는 것을 모른다.
understand though is why they would get
그들이 이해할 수있는 이유를 이해한다.
rid of it i mean this is such a popular
그것의 제거는 나가 이것이 그런 대중적 다는 것을 의미한다
thing i mean if you look at many social
당신이 많은 사교 활동
media there's always these collections
미디어에는 항상 이러한 컬렉션이 있습니다.
of all these great vine videos i mean i
이 모든 위대한 덩굴 비디오 중 내가 의미하는 것은
think of the one picture the guy is like
그 녀석이 좋아하는 한 그림을 생각해 보라.
story time and that'll do all these like
이야기 시간은 이것들을 좋아할거야.
story time i'm like hammer time exactly
이야기 시간 나는 망치처럼 정확하게 시간이다.
but like I I enjoyed these videos so I
하지만 II처럼이 비디오를 즐겼습니다.
don't understand why they're pulling the
그들이 왜 당기는 지 이해하지 못한다 .
plug I think it's my guess Twitter ain't
플러그 나는 내 생각에 트위터가 아닌 것 같아.
making money but it's not they gotta
돈을 벌지 만, 그렇지 않아.
start cutting back
뒤를 자르다
they're letting go a staff they're
그들은 직원들을 보내고있다.
letting go of services they're trying to
그들이 시도하고있는 서비스를 포기
bring themselves from here and get back
여기에서 스스로를 데리고 돌아 오다.
up to here get that but then sell it off
여기까지는 얻지 만 팔아 버리라.
I mean it's still wildly popular yeah
내말은 아직도 인기가 많아.
but i don't know i mean i will see what
하지만 나는 내가 무엇을 볼 것인지를 모른다는 것을 모른다.
happens next i know a guy who's a vine
다음에 나는 포도 나무 인 사람 을 안다.
star ii from here and berry but i don't
여기와 베리에서 별 2 세가되지만 나는 그렇지 않아.
know what he's gonna do now the ripe old
그가 지금 무엇 을 할 지 알지.
age you're like 22 i think he's gonna
당신이 22 같아 나이는 그가 거 같아요
have to get a real job he's gonna do
그가 할 일을 진짜해야 해.
something a lot longer than six seconds
6 초보다 훨씬 긴 뭔가.
look can I get your order of adults
나는 성인의 주문을받을 수 있니?
sorry what's up all right in other news
미안, 다른 뉴스에서 괜찮은거야.
an 18 year old has been charged with
18 년 된이 혐의로 기소 된
three counts of computer tampering after
3 회 컴퓨터 조작 후
accidentally swapping Arizona's
실수로 애리조나의
emergency services with thousands of
수천 개의 응급 서비스
bogus 911 telephone calls meet Kumar
가짜 911 전화는 쿠마르와 만난다.
hide to bat he decide told police he had
박쥐에게 숨어서 그는 그가 가진 경찰에게 결정했다.
tried to share on Twitter a link to
Twitter에 대한 링크를 공유하려고 시도 했습니다.
JavaScript code that exposed iOS bugs
iOS 버그를 노출 한 JavaScript 코드
making phones freeze or restart he had
전화가 멈추거나 그가 다시 시작하게 만들기
hoped Apple would pay him a bug bounty
애플이 버그 현상금을 지불하기를 바랐다.
for the information about the flaws but
결함 에 대한 정보 는
had mistakenly linked to an earlier
실수로 이전의
version of his app that made that that
그의 앱의 버전은
had made users phones keep on dialing
사용자의 전화가 전화 걸기를 계속하도록 만들었습니다.
911 a statement Maricopa County
성명서 Maricopa County
Sheriff's Office said the link had been
보안관 사무실은 그 링크가
clicked almost 2,000 times threatening
위협적으로 거의 2,000 번 클릭 함.
emergency services across Arizona
애리조나 전역의 응급 서비스
because the 911 service is classified as
911 서비스는 다음과 같이 분류되기 때문에
critical infrastructure interfering with
중요한 인프라가
its operation is treated in Arizona with
그것의 가동은에 애리조나에서 대우된다
the same severity as human trafficking
인신 매매와 같은 엄격함
or second degree murder Oh mm-hmm
또는 2 학년 살인 Oh mm-hmm
talking to police after his arrest mr.
체포 된 후 경찰과 이야기했다.
Desai said the bug he had been planning
Desai는 그가 계획하고 있던 버그를 말했다.
to exploit had been sent to him by an
악용하려는 사람은
online friend using it he intended
그가 사용하는 온라인 친구
exploiting it to make a benign but
양성으로 만들기 위해 그것을 착취하지만
annoying app that people would find
사람들이 찾을 수있는 짜증나는 앱
funny writing on the ARS technica news
ARS 테크니카 뉴스 에 재미있는 글
site Dan Goodin said the incident
사이트 댄 Goodin은 사건을 말했다
contained a valuable lesson for anyone
누구에게나 귀중한 교훈을 주었다.
getting started in security research
보안 연구 시작하기
hacking devices or networks without the
해킹 장치 또는 네트워크없이
explicit permission and cooperation of
명백한 허락과 협력
their owners is dangerous and can result
그들의 주인은 위험하고 결과를 낼 수있다.
in significant legal penalties I would
중대한 법적 형벌에서 나는
find this funny if it did
그랬다면이 재미있는 것을 찾아라.
not actually bring into play the 911
실제로 911을 가지고 놀지 마라.
situation because I can understand why
상황을 이해할 수 있기 때문에 상황
it with Perry like a second-degree
페리와 2 학년처럼
murder charge if you are hampering the
살인 혐의 당신이 방해하는 경우
response time for somebody who's
의 사람에 대한 응답 시간
actually in critical need that's a big
실제로 비판적 필요성이 크다.
deal and we haven't heard if anything
우리는 아무 것도 못 들었다 .
like that I mean how would they know
그런 뜻은 그들이 어떻게 알았 을까요?
right I can't get through to 911 they're
맞아, 나는 911에 이르지 못해.
swamped with these bogus calls calls
이 가짜 전화로 울부 짖었다.
from a piece of malware I'm a programmer
한 악성 코드에서 저는 프로그래머입니다.
and one of the things that you know I
내가 아는 것들 중 하나
adopted early on in my programming
내 프로그래밍 초기에 채택
career is you don't put things into code
경력은 코드에 물건을 넣지 않는 것입니다.
like automatically dial 911 or you know
자동으로 911에 전화 걸거나
swearing on in or silly things in in
안으로 또는 어리석은 것을 맹세하는
placeholders for example when you're
네가 할 때 예를 들어 자리 표시 자
developing something for someone because
누군가를 위해 뭔가를 개발했기 때문에
if that ever gets forgotten or you
그 적에게 잊어 도착하는 경우
forget to remove it hello you should
그것을 제거하는 것을 잊지 마세요.
have used lorem ipsum see and that's why
lorem ipsum 참조를 사용하고 그 이유는
it's there I I don't want to be that guy
거기에 내가 그 남자가되고 싶지 않아.
because I know I'm not that old but as
왜냐하면 나는 그 나이가 아니라
soon as the new started I here 18 year
새롭게 시작하자마자 여기서 18 년
old I'm gone Alex poor guy like he's not
늙은 나는 가난한 사람처럼 가난한 사람 알렉스.
really oh sure like life experience
인생 경험처럼 정말로 오.
makes you think about these met
당신 이 이것들에 대해 생각하게합니다.
ignorance isn't innocent by any means
무지가 어떤 의미로든 무죄가 아니다.
but there is no way he ever ever
그러나 그가 지금까지 결코 할 수있는 방법 이 없다.
intended this that's how it sounds yeah
의도 한 소리 예요
exact time when I was in my teens and I
십대에있을 때의 정확한 시간 과 나는
was getting into programming stuff I
프로그래밍에 들어갔다.
mean I know for myself I'm like what all
나는 나 자신을 위해 내가 모든 것을 좋아한다는 것을 안다는 것을 의미한다.
can I do how come how far can i push
내가 얼마나 멀리 밀어 넣을 수 있을까?
that I was writing autoexec.bat viruses
나는 autoexec.bat 바이러스를 작성하고 있었다.
well yeah nice tribute in them at school
잘 학교에서 그들에게 좋은 찬사.
in your team's you kind of like how far
당신 팀에서 너는 얼마나 멀었 니?
can i push this so I'm sure the guys 18
나는 이것을 밀어서 내가 남자 18 명이라고 확신 할 수 있을까?
I'm thinking chances are was some old
나는 나이가 들었다고 생각하고있다.
file that he created it was a mistake if
그는 그것이 실수하는 경우였다 만든 파일
it was Oh some 40 year old did it I go
오, 40 세 였어.
and I'll see that as a mistake but
그리고 저는 그것을 실수로 보았습니다.
that's just because I automatically
그건 내가 자동으로
default to ageism to hear 40 we expect
우리가 기대하는 40의 말을 듣기 위해 나이 그리기를 기본으로한다.
you to know better I feel bad for this
너 내가 더 잘 알기 위해서 이걸로 나쁘다.
poor kid personal record at 18 he can't
18 세의 가난한 어린이 개인 기록
even get that expunged I'm sure well he
심지어 그 사람을 도망 간다 나는 그가 틀림 없음을 확신한다.
wasn't convict
죄수가 아니 었어.
that was he was just charged he'll be
그 놈 이 방금 기소 됐을거야.
convicted yeah I don't know ah you may
유죄 판결을받은 나는 당신을 모른다.
have a plausible defense he needs
그가 필요한 그럴듯한 방어력을 가지고있다.
lawyers like these lawyers in this story
이 이야기에서이 변호사를 좋아하는 변호사
that's true okay uber drivers in Britain
그건 영국 의 진정한 우버 (Uber) 운전자들입니다.
should get paid vacation days and
유급 휴가를 얻고
guaranteed minimum wage a tribunal said
중재 재판소가 말한 최저 임금 보장
Friday in a ruling that the company will
금요일 회사가 결정할 것이라고 판결
appeal the Jeep megabytes labor union
지프 메가 바이트 노동 조합에 호소하다.
says the decision will have a major
결정은 주요있을 것이다 말한다
impact on the drivers who argued that
그것을 주장하는 운전자에게 미치는 영향
they should get the labor rights of
그들은 노동권을 얻어야한다.
employees not not self-employed workers
자영업자가 아닌 직원
the central London employment tribunals
런던 중심의 고용 재판소
decision Friday affects as many as
결정 금요일 많은 영향을 미칩니다.
30,000 drivers uber argues it is a
30,000 드라이버 uber 그것이 주장
technology company that links
기술 회사 링크
self-employed drivers with people who
자영업자와 운전자
need rides it also says drivers should
놀이기구를 필요로 또한 운전자가해야 말한다
seek arbitration in the Netherlands
네덜란드에서 중재를 구하라.
where ubers European operations are
ubers 유럽 사업은
based Nigel Mackay the attorney
니겔 매 케이 변호사
representing the workers argues uber
노동자를 대표하는 것은 우버
drivers often work very long hours just
운전자는 종종 매우 오랜 시간 동안 일합니다.
to earn enough to cover their basic
기본을 충당하기에 충분하다.
living costs it is the work carried out
생활비 수행 된 일
by these drivers that is allowed uber to
이 드라이버들에 의해
become the multi-billion dollar global
수십억 달러의 세계화
corporation that it is he goes on to say
그가 계속 해서 말하고있는 회사
we are pleased that the Employment
우리는 고용이
Tribunal has agreed with our arguments
재판소는 우리의 주장에 동의했습니다.
that drivers are entitled to the most
그 운전자는
basic workers rights including to be
기본 근로자의 권리를 포함하여
paid the national minimum wage and to
국가 최저 임금을 지불하고
receive paid holiday which were
유급 휴가를 받다
previously denied to them uber based in
이전에 거절당한
San Francisco California says it will
샌프란시스코 캘리포니아는
appeal the decision and not in the
결정에 호소 하고
meantime it only applies to the two
그 동안 두 사람에게만 적용됩니다.
people who brought the suit okay so ah
소송을 가져온 사람들은 괜찮아. 아.
those are pretty fantastic lawyers to
그 사람들은 꽤 환상적인 변호사 야.
make that happen really I I think that
정말 그렇게 생각해. 나는 그걸 생각해.
uber was always supposed to just be a
동네 짱은 항상 단지를해야했는데
supplementation to a regular income I
정기 수입 보충 전
don't think was ever supposed to be
이제까지이기 위하여 생각한 생각하지 말라.
full-time employment for anybody so I
누구를위한 풀 타임 고용 난 그렇게
don't know about paid vacation time yeah
유급 휴가 시간에 대해 모른다.
personally see okay this is a Jeff
개인적으로 이것이 제프임을 알았습니다.
question but yes he works for the the
질문을하지만 그는 예를 들어
unions yes my entire career is dealt in
노조 네, 내 경력 전체가 처리됩니다.
labor law so when this story came out it
노동법 때문에이 이야기가 나왔을 때
didn't matter what was happening around
주위에 무슨 일이 있었는지 중요하지 않았다.
me there could have been gunshots going
나도 총소리가 날 수 있었어.
off and I was going
나갔다.
to my phone reading this one I I've been
이 전화를 읽고있는 나의 전화에 나는 내가 있었다.
waiting for this decision I really have
난 정말이이 결정을 기다리고
ever since uber came around I've said
어버이가 돌아온 이래로 나는 말했다.
this was going to happen and there's a
이것은 일어날 예정이었고 거기에
couple reasons finelining it is a very
그것을 finelining 몇 가지 이유는 매우
fine line but I think there's a couple
좋은 줄로 생각하지만 부부가 있다고 생각합니다.
reasons for it and and one of them is
그것과 그 이유 중 하나는
the fact that it's they're not
그것이 그들이 아니란 사실.
entrepreneurs and self employed in the
기업가들과 자영업자들
fact that they're drumming up their own
그들이 자기 자신을 북돋는 사실.
business they have a company that is
사업 그들이하는 회사가
providing the work for them and while
그들 과 함께 일하는 동안
uber can try and argue that oh we're
위버는 우리가
just contracting them out there's no
그냥 계약을 맺지 않으면 안돼.
contractual agreement that says I am a
내가 계약했다고 말하는 계약 계약
subcontractor to over in the way that
하도급업자에게
it's set up it's I download the app I
그것은 내가 앱을 다운로드 한 것입니다.
just make it happen they find the work
그냥 일을 찾도록해라.
for me I work on their behalf they're
나를 위해 나는 그들을 위해 일한다.
the middleman with the money like
돈을 가진 중매인
everything about it to me screams
나에 대한 모든 것이 비명을 질렀다.
employment yeah does it does it start
고용 그래, 시작이야
does it start to feel like to you that
너 같은 기분이 들기 시작하니?
uber is like the company that is evading
uber는 회피 하는 회사와 같습니다.
taxes by putting their money abroad in a
해외에서 돈을 벌어 세금
way but they're doing it through their
그런데 그들은 그것들을 통해 그것을하고있다.
employees if you will the people who are
직원이 될 경우 직원
doing the work for them and this is
그들을 위해 일을하고 있으며 이것은
something I've never thought about until
내가 생각 해본 적도 없어.
this occurred I used to be a uber driver
이것은 우버 (Uber) 운전자였습니다.
you download like the driver app or
당신은 드라이버 앱처럼 다운로드하거나
whatever it is I've seen somebody with
그것이 무엇이든 나는 누군가를 보았다.
it I've never done it myself but you
그것은 나 자신을 결코 한 적이 없어 하지만 당신은
choose when you want to work you don't
당신이 원하지 않을 때 선택하십시오.
have to work anytime you don't want to
너는하고 싶지 않은 언제든지 일해야 해.
work is there a qualification process
거기 에 자격 과정이있다.
like there has to be a way I've never
내가 결코 해본 적이없는 방법이 있어야하는 것처럼
used uber but you have to record check I
사용 동네 짱하지만 당신은 내가 확인 기록해야
a criminal record check which is typical
전형적인 범죄 기록 수표
of me take a picture of it you take a
내가 찍은 사진을 찍어.
picture of your license a picture of
면허증 사진
your insurance and you upload it to them
당신의 보험 과 당신 이 그들에게 그것을 업로드 하십시오.
like an application yes when but you can
응용 프로그램과 같은 네 그러나 당신은 할 수
work for 15 minutes a week if you want
원한다면 일주일에 15 분간 일 하십시오.
or 15 minutes a month if you want you
원한다면 매월 15 분
can decline rides you can just straight
너는 곧바로 할 수있는 놀이기구를 거절 할 수있다.
up say no you don't want to do it what
너는 그걸하고 싶지 않아.
other job can you do that okay okay I
다른 일을 할 수 있니?
get that but the thing is I mean if you
알았어.하지만 너는
look at when the terrorist attack took
테러 공격이 언제 일어 났는지 살펴 보라.
place how did this turn to them
이 사람들이 어떻게 돌아 갔는가?
you're not you're not going in
너 안 갈거야?
Australia's remember the terrorist
호주는 테러리스트를 기억합니다.
attack in the coffee shop yeah it was a
커피 숍에서의 공격 예.
big PR nightmare for uber because when
언제나 큰 언론의 악몽
that terrorist attack hit they have
테러 공격이 그들에게 닥쳤다.
their software based on demand sets the
수요에 따라 소프트웨어를
prices and the prices skyrocketed to
가격과 가격이 폭등했다.
like a hundred bucks a kilometer just to
방금 1 백 킬로미터처럼
get people out of the core the downtown
시내 중심에서 사람들을 내쫓다
core when the when the shots started
코어가 시작될 때
firing and so if you are a contractor
해고 해서 계약자 라면
chances are you're setting your own rate
기회는 당신이 당신 자신의 속도를 정하고있다.
uber is setting those rates you are just
uber는 당신이 정당한 비율을 정하고 있습니다.
the driver so when you look at that kind
운전사는 당신이 그런 종류를 볼 때
of stuff Uber's in complete control of
Uber가 완벽하게 통제 할 수있는
every element of that job the only thing
그 직업의 모든 요소 는 유일한 것
they don't have control over is your
그들은 통제력이 없습니다.
hands on the steering wheel hmm and so
스티어링 휠에 손 흠. 그래서
from the bat bat by look at and I go I
봐서 박쥐 박쥐 에서 그리고 나는 간다.
think it's a very valid argument that
그것은 매우 유효한 논쟁이라고 생각합니다.
they are in fact employees yeah i work
그들은 사실 내가 일하는 직원이다.
for a company who sets what we charge
우리가 청구하는 것을 설정하는 회사
the customer and what I get paid does
고객과 제가받는 돈은 어떻게됩니까?
that sound like anyone you know rhymes
당신이 아는 사람처럼 그 소리가 운율
with Boober but you're an employee I'm
Boober와 함께하지만 당신은 종업원입니다.
an employee yes yeah yeah but do you get
직원 예 예 예하지만 당신은 얻을
to point in case you get to decline work
직장을 거절 할 경우를 대비해서
I get to decline work if I want to
내가 원한다면 나는 일을 거절하게된다.
decline work i will decline work
거절 일 나는 거절 할거야.
absolutely i am the red flag okay so I'm
절대적으로 나는 빨간 깃발이다. 그래서 나는 그렇다.
like forty-nine percent on your side
너의 편 에서는 49 % 를 좋아해.
really yeah determined that much
정말 그래 그 정도 결정
49-percent not 48 it's all I didn't have
49 퍼센트가 아니라 48 퍼센트는 내가 가지고 있지 않은 것 전부다.
to get myself see a majority on this one
이 대다수를 볼 수있게 하려면
only because I kinda empty mber she's
나는 그녀가 비어 있기 때문에 단지 비어있다.
like I am going to be a new driver right
나는 새로운 운전자가 될거야.
after the show do with with weather uber
공연이 끝나고 날씨 우버와 함께
is a great service or not sure I mean I
훌륭한 서비스 이거나 확실하지 않다는 뜻입니다.
what are they what are they defined as
그들이 무엇을 정의 했는가?
right I don't think that you can be an
네가 네가 할 수 있다고 생각하지 않아 .
uber driver and work 15 minutes a month
uber 드라이버 및 작업 15 분
and get vacation pay you know well that
휴가를 보내면 잘 알게 될거야.
no no no no because then you'd be part
아니, 아니, 아니, 아니, 그때 너는 일부가 될거야.
time okay okay but the people who What's
시간 괜찮아. 하지만 사람들은 뭐야?
in question here is the people who are
문제의 사람들은
putting in 15-hour days like a taxi
택시처럼 15 시간 동안두기.
driver right should they be compensated
운전자는 보상을 받아야한다.
like a taxi driver regardless whether
여부에 관계없이 택시 운전사처럼
they want to be an irregularly scheduled
그들은 불규칙적으로 예정되고 싶어한다.
employee that picks up shifts on their
직원이 자신의 업무를
choice of me when I worked for the
내가 일할 때 나를 선택했다.
government I could turn down any shift I
정부는 어떤 변화도 거절 할 수있다.
wanted if I didn't want to go in for a
내가 들어가기를 원하지 않으면 원했다.
month I didn't go in for
한 달 동안 나는 들어 가지 않았다.
but I i picked up the work is that just
하지만 난이 일이 있다는 것입니다 집어 단지
before you got fired but i mean i was
당신은 해고 그러나 도착하기 전에 내가 있었다 의미
always available to work I mean you look
항상 일할 수 있습니다.
at where it was going where they're
그들이 어디로 가는지
looking to do uber air with flights yeah
비행과 함께 uber 공기를 찾고 예
I mean are they gonna say that I mean if
내 말은 그들이 만약 내가
I'm gonna hop into a plane and have them
나는 비행기에 뛰어 들어가서 그들을 가질거야.
fly me I can guarantee you you're gonna
날 날 비켜 줄거야.
sign up to be an uber part I hope that
uber 부분에 가입 해야합니다.
they are an employee is on the hook cuz
그들은 직원이 후크 사촌에있다
if that plane goes down I don't want my
비행기가 다운되면 내가 원하지 않는 내
family suing just some random guy who
닥치는대로의 사람을 고소하고있는 가족
you know crash the plane I want to make
내가 만들고 싶은 비행기 가 추락하는 것을 안다.
sure that uber is on the hook and if you
위버가 후크에 있는지 , 그리고
look at there's a something with amazon
아마존과 무언가가있어.
i want to say with one of the states if
나는 국가들 중 하나와 이야기하고 싶다.
you can't get hold of this came out just
너는 이것을 잡을 수 없다. 그냥 나왔다.
yeah okay i think it was if you if you
좋아 그래 내가 그것을 생각하면 만약 당신이 경우
can't get a hold of the company that
회사를 붙잡을 수 없다.
sold you bad product you can go after
나쁜 제품을 팔았습니다.
the seller so does that mean if in this
판매자도 그렇게한다.
case that they could also go after uber
그들은 또한 우버에게 갈 수있는 경우
I mean that's a whole nother legal side
나는 그것이 법적인면에서 전체적으로 중요하다는 것을 의미한다.
of it but I I totally think totally
그것의 II 그러나 나는 완전히 완전히 생각한다.
think they are employees see the comment
그들은 직원들이 의견을 보았다고 생각한다.
thing below see that field down there
그 아래의 필드를 아래에서 본다.
please comment on this post your
이 게시물에 의견을 남기십시오.
comments I don't resolve the
의견 나는이 문제를 해결하지 못한다.
conversation below I think in the
아래의 대화는 내가 생각하기에
comment section well team stats on this
코멘트 섹션 잘 팀 통계 이것에
one nope facebook inc's software knows
하나의 nope facebook inc의 소프트웨어는 알고있다.
your face almost as well as your mother
당신의 얼굴 은 거의 당신 어머니뿐입니다.
does and like mom it isn't asking your
엄마는 엄마를 좋아하지 않는다.
permission to do what it wants with old
낡은 것으로 원하는대로 할 수있는 허가
photos facebook encourages users to tag
사진 facebook은 사용자에게 태그 를 달라고합니다.
people in photographs that they upload
사진을 업로드 한 사람들
in their personal posts and social
개인 게시물 및 소셜
network stores the collected information
네트워크 는 수집 된 정보를 저장합니다.
the company uses a program it calls deep
회사는 깊은 곳에서 전화하는 프로그램을 사용합니다.
face to match other photos of a person
사람의 다른 사진과 일치하는 얼굴
to match the other photos of a person
사람의 다른 사진과 일치시키기
alphabet inks cloud-based google photos
알파벳 잉크 구름 기반 Google 포토
service uses similar technology while
서비스가 유사한 기술을 사용하는 동안
millions of internet users embrace the
수백만 명의 인터넷 사용자가
tagging of family and friends in photos
사진에서 가족과 친구들의 태그 달기
others worried that there's something
다른 사람들이 뭔가 있다고 걱정했다.
devious afoot are trying to block
악의적 인 일이 막으려하고있다.
facebook as well as Google from amassing
페이스 북은 물론 Google과의 만남
such data as advances in facial
얼굴의 진보와 같은 데이터
recognition technology give companies
인식 기술, 기업에 제공
the potential to profit from biometric
생체 인식으로 이익을 얻을 수있는 잠재력
data privacy advocates see a pattern in
데이터 프라이버시 옹호자들은
how the world's largest social network
세계 최대의 소셜 네트워크
and search engine have sold users
검색 엔진이 사용자를 팔았습니다.
viewing histories for advert
광고에 대한 히스토리보기
the company's insists that gathering
이 회사 는
data on what you look like isn't against
당신이 닮은 것에 대한 데이터 는 반대가 아닙니다.
the law even without your permission if
귀하의 허락없이도 법률
judges agree with Facebook and Google
판사는 Facebook과 Google에 동의합니다.
they may be able to kill off lawsuits
그들은 소송을 죽일 수 있습니다
filed under your unique Illinois law
당신의 독특한 일리노이 법에 따라 제출
that carries find of one one thousand
1 천 개가 발견되는
two $5,000 us each time a person's image
한 사람의 이미지가 나올 때마다 2 천 달러 씩
is used without permission big enough
충분히 큰 허가없이 사용
for a liability headache if claims on
에 대한 클레임이
behalf of millions of consumers proceed
수백만 명의 소비자를 대신하여
as class actions a loss by the companies
집단 행동으로 기업의 손실
could lead to new restrictions on using
사용에 대한 새로운 제한을 초래할 수있다.
biometric in the US similar to those in
미국의 생체 인식
Europe and Canada Wow see I didn't know
유럽 과 캐나다 와우 내가 모르는 걸 본다.
that we had restrictions in Canada but I
우리는 캐나다에서 제한을 받았지만
will tell you that that whole like deep
그 모든 것이 깊은 것 같다고 말할 것입니다.
face technology always mistakes me and
얼굴 기술은 항상 나를 실수로합니다.
my sisters as each other oh yeah so for
오, 그래, 내 여동생 서로
me it's just funny because yeah well
나 잘 지내기 때문에 그냥 재미있어.
that's pretty small scale now i have i
꽤 작은 규모에요.
have like little star trek trinkets
작은 별처럼 트레킹 장신구가있다.
around the studio and everything we used
스튜디오 주변과 우리가 사용한 모든 것
to have a bobblehead that was Spock so
Spock이었던 범블 헤드 를 가지고있다.
and I have things all over the studio
스튜디오 곳곳에 물건이 있어요.
like my coaster right and and and it's
내 코스터 좋아해요.
not just these companies that are doing
하고있는 이들 회사 만이 아닙니다.
at Twitter was experimenting with it for
트위터에서 그것을 실험 하고 있었다.
a while there and I don't see that they
그곳에있는 동안 나는 그들이 보이지 않는다.
still use it but they must in the back
여전히 사용하지만 뒷면에 있어야합니다.
end I had a studio picture that i posted
끝 나는 스튜디오 그림을 내가 게시했다.
and twitter said Robbie Ferguson posted
트위터에 따르면 로비 퍼거슨 (Robbie Ferguson)은
this with Leonard Nimoy and it had a tag
Leonard Nimoy와 함께이 태그에 태그가 있습니다.
going to his Twitter account Wow and
그의 트위터 계정에 와우와
that freaked me right out like I was
내가처럼 맞아 밖으로 저를 흥분
like okay that's cool for one thing the
좋아요. 그건 한 가지 멋진 데요.
technology is astonishing but also a
기술은 놀랍습니다.
little bit creepy but at the same time
조금은 오싹하지만 동시에
creepy but cool the creepy but cool I
소름 끼치는하지만 시원한하지만 소름 끼치는하지만 난
think it's the next-gen of where things
그것이 사물의 다음 세대 라고 생각해.
are going to have to go for surveillance
감시 를해야 할 것 같아.
and you're gonna see it when it comes to
그것이 올 때 당신은거야 그것을 볼 수있어
you know we talked about you know the
너는 우리가 너에 대해서 이야기 했다는 것을 안다.
threats that are out there and they have
밖에있는 위협과 그들이 가지고있는 위협
to be able to track these things AKA
이런 일들을 추적 할 수있다.
person of interest right i mean truth be
관심있는 사람 은 진실을 의미합니다.
told they have CCTV everywhere in Europe
그들은 유럽 전역에 CCTV를 가지고 있다고 말했다.
right now so I mean I meant this and
지금이 말은 내가 이것을 의미한다는 것을 의미한다.
integrate this and boom and there's a
이것과 붐을 통합하면
little bit you have to be a little bit
약간 조금 있으면 될거야.
worried I want to use that 23andme
그 23andme 를 사용 하고 싶다.
genetic testing but I'm scared that I'm
유전자 검사를 받았지만 나는 두렵다.
sending my DNA to somebody who I don't
내 DNA를 내가 아는 누군가에게 보냈다.
know I I want to know the results
나는 그 결과를 알고 싶어한다는 것을 알고있다.
okay I know that I'm the guy that for
알았어. 나는 그 녀석이야.
some reason defaults to conspiracy
음모를 꾸미는 어떤 이유
theory and Manti robots taking us over
이론과 우리를 데려 간 Manti 로봇
and all that kind of stuff but I'm not
그 모든 종류의 물건들 그러나 나는 그런 것이 아니다.
why does this one come as a shock like
왜 이건 충격 같은거야?
technology is going this way why are
기술은 왜 이렇게 될까요?
people freaking out about it as if it's
사람들이 마치 그것처럼 마약 중독자
like some big issue I've known this is
몇 가지 큰 문제처럼이는 알고 있었다
coming for a while I think from its
잠시 동안 내가 생각하기에
science fiction gone reality well yeah
공상 과학 소설 현실은 물론 그래
but I mean this is this you're right
하지만 이 말이 당신 말이 맞아요.
what's this situation is we're dealing
이 상황이 뭐지?
with it from a legal standpoint and not
법적 관점에서 볼 때
looking at it from a morality standpoint
도덕적 견지 에서 그것을보고있다.
and our world globally has moved away
우리의 세계는 전 세계적으로 사라졌습니다.
from the human element to the legal
인간의 요소에서 합법적 인 요소로
element and we are now legal entities as
우리는 현재 법인으로
far as our own basic human rights we're
우리 자신의 기본 인권 과 마찬가지로
nothing more than contractual
계약적인 것 이상
obligations but do's and don't it does
의무는 있지만 그렇게하지 마라.
it violate my rights that my picture is
그것은 나의 그림이있는 나의 권리를 침해한다.
recognized by an artificial intelligence
인공 지능으로 인정받는
when if I'm standing in a room sash I
언제 내가 방 띠줄에 서있으면
can see me from across room say oh
방 건너편 에서 나를 볼 수 있다. 오.
there's recognized know what to do with
뭘해야하는지 알았어.
you yes what to do with me that's the
너와 나랑 무슨 상관이야.
issue is they're saying like fly a drone
그들이 비행기를 드론처럼 말하는거야.
in and no should be in a hedge with a
에 어떠한 기호가있는 헤지에 없어야합니다
rubber bullet this this whole thing is
이 총알은 고무 총알입니다.
saying you shouldn't be able to use my
내 말을 사용해서는 안된다는 거야.
biometrics to earn a profit and I have
생체 인식은 이익을 얻고 나는 가지고있다.
tits data data is money that's the
가슴 데이터 데이터는 돈이다.
currency why is Windows 10 free yeah and
통화가 왜 Windows 10 무료 예 및
Facebook is free I get that exactly
페이스 북은 자유 롭다 나는 그것을 정확하게 얻는다.
that's exactly the business I know for
그게 내가 아는 사업이야.
something that's completely free nothing
아무것도 완전히 무료 인 무언가
is free I let people know that yeah we
나는 사람들에게 우리가
talked about apps they sure ask for all
그들이 모두를 요구하는 앱에 대해 이야기했습니다.
this access because it's a free app you
이 앱은 무료 앱이므로이 액세스 권한이 있습니다.
want those out by not downloading the
다운로드하지 않기를 원하는 사람들
app yeah exactly and this is the thing I
정확히 그래 ,이 앱 은 내가하는 일이다.
mean Facebook changed the way that we do
페이스 북이 우리가하는 방식을 바꿨다는 것을 의미합니다.
the world before Facebook it was you had
페이스 북 이전의 세계 는 당신이 가진 것이 었습니다.
to give explicit permissions for
에 대한 명시적인 권한 부여
anything to happen and then Zuckerberg
일어나고 Zuckerberg에 무엇이든
and his and his team came up with this
그의 팀이 이걸 생각해 냈어.
brilliant idea to say you use our app
우리의 앱을 사용한다고 말하는 뛰어난 아이디어
yeah you're volunteering if we're giving
우리가주는다면 네가 자원하고있어.
on everything and you tell us what not
모든 것에 대해
to use and and we'll change that halfway
사용하고, 우리는 그것을 반쯤 바꿀 것입니다.
through after that now after you've said
그 후에 너는 말했다.
no will eventually just say yes and you
no는 결국 yes와 you라고 말할 것입니다.
have to go back and find it as a it
돌아가서 그것을 찾아야 해.
Milligan moral landscape absolutely it
Milligan 도덕적 풍경 절대적으로 그것
is changing remember back in
기억을 다시 변화시키고있다.
interrogation not that I've ever been an
내가 지금까지 해왔 던 적이 아닌 심문
interrogation room but they used to try
취조실하지만 그들은 시도하는 데 사용
and like drag information out of you but
정보를 끄집어 내듯이
who your friends are and who you were
당신 친구가 누구이고 누구 였는지
and everything and now all I have to do
그리고 모든 것과 내가해야 할 모든 것
is go on your facebook and be like oh I
당신의 페이스 북에 가서 오처럼 될 수 있습니다.
have a list of all of your friends I
너의 모든 친구들 의 목록을 나 가지고있어.
know exactly where you've been I know
내가 아는 곳을 정확히 알아라 .
what you've eaten in the past 14 days
지난 14 일 동안 먹은 음식
yeah they have everything now we have
그래, 그들은 우리가 가진 모든 것을 가지고있다.
pictures to prove it you know that it's
사진이 있다는 것을 증명하는 사진
not the end of the world though I mean
내 말은 아니지만 세계 의 끝이 아니야.
this is the way technology is going the
이것은 기술이가는 방식입니다 .
way that we will know that the
우리가 알게 될
apocalypse has come is when robots take
로봇이 걸릴 때 종말이왔다.
over our kitchen I mean it's not
우리 부엌에서 나는 그렇지 않다는 뜻이다.
possible right it's never ever going to
가능하다면 절대로 갈 수 없다.
happen it's true well apparently having
그것은 분명히 사실 일 것입니다.
home-cooked meal from the kitchen of
부엌 에서 집에서 조리 한 식사
Gordon Ramsay could become a reality in
고든 램지의 현실이 될 수 있습니다
2018 moley will launch the world first
2018 년 몰리브덴 , 세계 최초 출시
fully automated and integrated
완전히 자동화되고 통합 된
intelligent cooking robots what yes it's
지능형 조리 로봇
a robotic kitchen that has unlimited
무제한의 로봇 주방
access to chefs and their recipes
요리사와 조리법에 대한 접근성
worldwide and not only can this robotic
전세계 뿐만 아니라이 로봇 수 있습니다
chef cook over 100 different meals for
요리사가 100 가지 이상의 다양한 식사를 제공합니다.
you it will clean up after itself to
너 스스로 청소 해 줄거야.
bless you robot according to Mark Olynyk
Mark Olynyk 에 따르면 당신에게 축복을 베풀어 라.
CEO and founder of moley robotics the
몰리 로봇의 CEO 겸 창업자
way this machine works for the end user
이 기계가 최종 사용자를 위해 작동하는 방식
is by specifying the number of portions
부분 수를 지정하는 것입니다.
type of cuisine dietary restrictions
식단 제한의 종류
calorie counts desired ingredients
칼로리는 원하는 성분을 센다.
cooking method and chef and so on for
요리 방법과 요리사 등
the recipe from the recipe library first
래서 피 라이브러리 의 래서 피 먼저
then with a single tap you could choose
한 번 탭하면 선택할 수 있습니다.
your recipe place the individual
귀하의 제조법은 개인을 배치
prepackaged containers of measured
미리 포장 된 측정 용기
washed and cut ingredients on designated
지정 성분을 씻어서 자른다.
spots and press start for the cooking
점을 찍고 조리 를 시작합니다 .
process to begin moley consists of all
몰리브덴을 시작하는 과정은 모두로 구성된다.
the necessary cabinetry appliances and
필요한 캐비닛기구 및
utensils it starts with two special
기구는 두 개의 특수한 도구로 시작합니다.
sensors which record each movement of
각 운동을 기록하는 센서
the actual MasterChef while they cook
그들이 요리하는 동안 실제 마스터 셰프
away wearing special gloves this kitchen
멀리 특별한 장갑을 끼고이 부엌
then replicates the movement with two
그 다음에 두 개의
fully articulating robotic arms and can
로봇 팔을 완벽하게 관절 식으로 조종 할 수있다.
cook anything just like a human chef but
인간 요리사 처럼 아무것도 요리하지 말고
since the whole kitchen could
부엌 전체가
essentially cook any downloadable recipe
본질적으로 다운로드 가능한 요리법 요리
on the internet
인터넷에
food robotics AI startup expects to
AI 로봇 시동 로봇
include a share and sell your own
공유를 포함하고 자신의 것을 판매하십시오.
recipes feature where consumers and
조리법은 소비자와 소비자가
professional chefs could access and sell
전문 요리사가 접근하고 팔 수있다.
their ideas via the digital style
디지털 스타일을 통한 아이디어
library of recipes database designed to
래서 피 데이터베이스의 라이브러리
work with anyone who has the desire and
욕망 이 있는 사람 과
the ability to cook this platform for
이 플랫폼을 요리 할 수있는 능력
collective creativity and knowledge
공동 창의력과 지식
could become a launching pad for
에 대한 발사대가 될 수있다.
aspiring chefs while you may need a
당신이 필요로하는 동안 요리사를 꿈꾸는
Wi-Fi for pulling in new recipes
새 조리법을 가져 오는 Wi-Fi
recording a new dish or sharing your
새로운 요리를 녹음하거나
work the database of recipes that comes
오는 조리법 의 데이타베이스를 일하십시오
with the kitchen is available offline
부엌은 오프라인에서 사용할 수 있습니다.
what's more the robotic kitchen can
로봇 키친은 무엇보다
always be used manually to questions
수동으로 항상 질문에 사용
comments thought you know what I think
의견은 내가 생각 하는 것을 당신이 알고 있다고 생각했다.
is the first thing the first thing that
가장 먼저 할 일은
came to mind is what right but then I
마음이 떠오르지 만 그때 나는 옳다.
really think about educational
교육에 대해 정말로 생각해보십시오.
facilities where the teacher could
교사가 할 수있는 시설
download these recipes and actually use
이 조리법을 다운로드하고 실제로 사용하십시오
it to guide would be chefs to learn now
그것은 배우기 위해 요리사가 될 것입니다.
of course there's the other side of it
물론 그 반대편이있다.
that says they're gonna you know Gordon
그들이 고든을 알게 될거라고 말했어.
Ramsay can now open a thousand kitchens
램지는 이제 천개의 부엌을 열 수 있습니다.
around the world and it will be his
전 세계에 있으며 그의 것입니다
cooking yeah that's true i was thinking
요리 그래, 그건 사실이야 내가 생각하고 있었어.
more along the lines of having say your
당신의 말을 따라 가면서
grandmother make her her on yeah and
할머니가 그녀를 예쁘게 만들고
then you can eat grandma's lasagna oh my
할머니의 라자냐를 먹을 수있어. 오, 내
god time right you not only but that
신 시간이 바로 당신을뿐만 아니라,하지만
made me think see we were just playing
우리가 그냥 놀고 있었다고 생각하게 만들었 어.
off of each other right here what about
여기서 서로에 대해
grandma when she can't cook that lasagna
할머니가 그 라자냐를 요리 할 수 ​​없을 때 할머니.
anymore but she loves to eat it right
더 이상 그녀 는 그것을 먹기를 좋아한다.
right I love this so much oh my gosh
맞아, 이거 너무 좋아.
there's so much here told I'm not a
너무 많이 여기있어 .
great cook like I'm not a super great
내가 위대 하지는 않은 것처럼 훌륭한 요리사.
cook but I want to be so this would be
요리사가되고 싶지만 그렇게되고 싶다 .
great for me I could just watch this
나를 위해 위대한 나는 단지 이것을 볼 수 있었다.
robot cook and then like it said I mean
로봇 요리사가 말했듯이 내가 말한 것처럼
I can just turn off the probably the
아마 그저 아마
arms and not gonna happen no great
팔이 아니라 큰 일이 없을거야.
you're just gonna sit there drinking
너 거기 앉아서 술 마시는 거야.
your whiskey watch my robot robot song
위스키, 내 로봇 로봇 노래보기
make me okay I love it how do you how do
내가 좋아하게 해줘. 내가 얼마나 좋아하는지 어떻게 생각해?
you feel about this Jeff alright here
당신은 확실히 여기 제프 대해 어떻게 생각
comes the opinion folks so we know how I
우리가 어떻게 알 수 있도록 의견이 나온다.
feel about robots taking over the world
세계를 점령하고있는 로봇에 대한 느낌
this is just the kitchen I realized this
이건 내가 깨달은 부엌 일 뿐이야.
is just
단지
kitchen as you're reading the news story
당신이 뉴스 기사를 읽는 동안 주방
there's one question that's coming up in
한 가지 질문이 있습니다.
my head and it goes back to the you made
내 머리와 너는 다시 너를 만들었다.
the comment that there's two sensors
두 개의 센서가 있다는 의견
that watch what the chef is doing so the
주방장이하고있는 일을 지켜봐.
question is in the middle of making a
질문은
beef wellington will these hands drop
쇠고기 웰링턴이 손을 놓을 것입니다.
the knife flip the bird and then call
칼이 새를 뒤집은 다음 전화
somebody oh Gordon Ramsay oh Gordon
누군가 오 고든 램지 오 고든
Ramsay what have you done with this
램지, 이걸로 뭘 했니?
program what can he cook any meal
그가 무엇을 요리 할 수있는 프로그램
without doing something like that yeah
그런 식으로하지 않고
like there's no auditory component
청각 적 구성 요소가없는 것처럼
that's fantastic oh I bet you they'll
그거 환상적이야. 그들이 너를 걸 겠어.
included yeah I the other question is
다른 질문 이 포함되어 있습니다.
I'm sitting here between Sasha and
나는 사샤와
Robbie and both of you are talking about
로비와 둘 다 얘기하고있어.
replacing grandma with a robot no it's
할머니를 로봇으로 바꾸는 건 아니야.
about supplementing grandma like with a
할머니를 보충하는 것과
robot helping grandma so that she can
할머니가 할 수있게 도와주는 로봇
cook once and eat her lasagna for author
한 번 요리하고 저자를 위해 라자냐를 먹는다.
I do believe it was grandma's lasagna
나는 할머니의 라자냐라고 생각한다.
then you could have it till the end of
그 다음엔 끝날 때까지 가질 수 있어요.
time implying when grandma passes away
할머니가 돌아가시기를 암시하는 시간
she's replaced by robotics but you can
그녀는 로봇으로 대체되었지만
eat her lasagna you can pass the
그녀의 라자냐를 먹어라.
delicious taste on that's true what my
그 맛있는 맛은 내
thought is more and if they have to do
생각은 더 많습니다.
with your stomach say well but why not
너 위가 잘 말한다. 왜 안돼?
just learn to cook the lasagna no yeah
그냥 라자냐를 요리하는 법 을 배워라.
of course but there's something about
물론 뭔가가 있습니다.
grandmas robot hands cooking you up a
할머니 로봇 손 요리
lasagna while you said they're drinking
네가 술을 마시고있는 동안 라자냐
your whiskey okay okay let's take this
위스키 좋아 , 이걸 가져 가자.
like let's take this on the poutine turn
이걸 푸틴 군대 차례대로 가져 가자.
ok so today careful how you bring up
좋아, 오늘 조심해.
poutine that is a sacred form I know but
내가 알고 있는 신성한 형태 인 푸틴.
what I'm saying is i am talking in the
무슨 말인지 내가 얘기를하고있다
chat room but how poutine is amazing
대화방이 아니라 어떻게 poutine가 놀랍 니?
yesterday and they don't get it they
어제 그들은 그것을 얻지 못한다.
don't get it cuz they're not some canada
그것들을 사지 마라. 그들은 캐나다가 아니야.
so what if i upload how like a delicious
그래서 내가 얼마나 맛좋은 지 업로드하면 어떨까요?
poutine wrestle sure yeah but right and
Poutine은 네,하지만 맞습니다.
then they're robots can make it and then
그러면 로봇은 그것을 만들 수 있습니다.
they can understand okay yeah yeah what
그들은 이해할 수 있습니다. 예. 예.
kind of poutine are you making a
Poutine의 종류는 당신이 만드는거야?
requires robotic it's fries gravy cheese
로봇식이 필요합니다 그레이비 치즈 튀김
curds think about that yeah it's gotta
곱슬 곱슬하게 생각 해봐야 해.
be Kurt spade a minute what if you do
네가해야한다면 커트 스페이드가 될거야.
the poutine recipe and I you did the
poutine 요리법과 나는 너를했다.
recording and it was this nice
녹음이 좋았어.
russet potato and then Jeff takes it
황갈색 감자를 먹은 다음 Jeff가 가져 간다.
home and loads up the recipe and he's
집으로 가서 요리법을로드하면 그는
got this larger potato and the
이 큰 감자와있어
ingredients and the recipe the mix
재료와 조리법 믹스
everything is completely I feel like
모든게 완전히 기분이 좋아.
they must have controls for that they
그들은 그들에 대한 통제력을 가져야한다.
have total I couldn't remain a mystery
나는 수수께끼로 남아있을 수 없다.
but it did say about prepackaged food
그러나 그것은 미리 포장 된 음식에 대해 말했습니다.
and all that kind of stuff right
그 모든 종류의 일들이 바로
essentially this is nothing more than a
본질적으로 이것은 아무것도 아니다 .
glorified microwave no no this is fresh
영광 된 마이크로파 아니, 아니 신선하지 않아.
food this is not but instead of new
이것은 새로운 것이 라기보다는 음식이다.
package you can't have Rebecca no you
당신은 더 당신에게 레베카를 가질 수 없습니다 패키지로 만듭니다
can go into a grocery store and buy a
식료품 가게에 가서 구입하실 수 있습니다
pre-cut up fresh turnip yes right way
신선한 순 무를 미리 잘라내 네. 맞아.
easier than cutting her and turnip right
그녀와 순무를 자르는 것보다 쉽다.
but so now take that and put that on a
하지만 이제 그것을 취해서
tray and say okay now robot make me a
쟁반, 이제 로봇이 나에게
turkey dinner and it includes the
칠면조 저녁 식사와
pre-cut turn I don't know what I can we
미리 커팅 턴 내가 뭘 할 수 있는지 모르겠다.
enjoy still would rally yeah let's
랠리 그래, 즐기자.
interview them let's go Thank You Molly
인터뷰 해 주셔서 감사합니다. 몰리
let's get a dozen of these moly kitchens
이 열 여덟 개의 부엌을 갖자.
and we just really i'd rather make my
그리고 우린 단지 정말로
bowl of Cheerios myself oh yeah just
치리의 그릇 자신 오, 그래 단지
scratch aim high reach the stars thanks
스크래치 목표 높은 별에 도달 감사
for watching the category 5 TV news room
카테고리 5 시청을 위한 TV 뉴스 룸
don't forget to like and subscribe for
좋아하고 구독 하는 것을 잊지 마세요.
all your tech news with a slight linux
약간의 리눅스로 모든 기술 뉴스
bias and for more free content be sure
편견과 더 많은 자유로운 내용을 위해
to check out our website from the
우리의 웹 사이트를
category 5 TV news room and sasha
카테고리 5 TV 뉴스 룸 및 사샤
tomatoes
토마토